<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Durban Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <string name="nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>

    <!--Strings used in the MuseumFragment-->
    <string name="natural_science_museum">Durban Natural Science Museum</string>
    <string name="nsm_address">First Floor, City Hall, Anton Lembede Street</string>
    <string name="old_house_museum">The Old House Museum</string>
    <string name="ohm_address">31 Diaconia Street, City Centre</string>
    <string name="kwamuhle_museum">KwaMuhle Museum</string>
    <string name="km_address">130 Bram Fischer Road, City Centre</string>
    <string name="campbell_collection">The Campbell Collection</string>
    <string name="cc_address">220 Gladys Mazibuko Road</string>
    <string name="port_natal_museum">Port Natal Maritime Museum</string>
    <string name="pnm_address">Maritime Place, Small Craft Harbour, City Centre</string>
    <string name="phansi_museum">Phansi Museum</string>
    <string name="pm_address">500 Esther Roberts Road, Glenwood</string>
    <string name="cato_manor_heritage_center">Cato Manor Heritage Center</string>
    <string name="cmhc_address">Intuthuko Junction, 750 Rick Turner Road, Cato Manor</string>
    <string name="old_court_house">The Old Court House</string>
    <string name="och_address">99 Samora Machel Street, City Centre</string>
    <string name="bergtheil_museum">Bergtheil Museum</string>
    <string name="bm_address">16 Queens Avenue, Westville</string>

    <!--Strings used in the RestaurantFragment-->
    <string name="cafe_1999">Cafe 1999</string>
    <string name="address_cafe_1999">Shop 2, Silvervause Centre, 117 Vause Rd, Musgrave</string>
    <string name="butcher_boys">Butcher Boys Florida Road</string>
    <string name="address_butcher_boys">170 Florida Rd, Morningside</string>
    <string name="avenue_bistro">9th Avenue Bistro</string>
    <string name="address_avenue_bistro">2, Avonmore centre, 9th Ave, Morningside</string>
    <string name="little_india">The Little India Restaurant</string>
    <string name="address_little_india">155 Musgrave Rd, Berea</string>
    <string name="grill_jichana">Grill Jichana</string>
    <string name="address_grill_jichana">Southern Sun Elangeni &amp; Maharani, 63 Snell Parade, North Beach</string>
    <string name="mali">Mali\'s Indian Restaurant</string>
    <string name="address_mali">77 Smiso Nkwanyana Rd, Morningside</string>
    <string name="quo_restaurant">Quo Restaurant</string>
    <string name="address_quo_restaurant">Gillitts Shopping Centre, 2 Clifton Rd, Gillitts</string>
    <string name="joops_place">Joops Place</string>
    <string name="address_joops_place">14, Avonmore Centre, NINTH Avenue, Essenwood</string>
    <string name="surf_riders">Surf Riders Food Shack</string>
    <string name="address_surf_riders">17 Erskine Terrace, South Beach</string>
    <string name="afro">Afro\'s Chicken Shop</string>
    <string name="address_afro">2 O R Tambo Parade, South Beach</string>
    <string name="jack_salmon">Jack Salmon Fish House</string>
    <string name="address_jack_salmon">Shop 15, Glenore Centre, 1 Aubrey Dr, Glen Ashley</string>
    <string name="olive_oil">Olive &amp; Oil</string>
    <string name="address_olive_oil">149 Helen Joseph Road, Glenwood</string>
    <string name="mooki_noodle_bar">Mooki Noodle Bar</string>
    <string name="address_mooki_noodle_bar">190 Brand Rd, Glenwood</string>
    <string name="lupa_osteria">Lupa Osteria</string>
    <string name="address_lupa_osteria">124 Jan Hofmeyr Rd, Dawncrest, Westville</string>
    <string name="big_easy">Big Easy Durban by Ernie Els</string>
    <string name="address_big_easy">12\-14 Walnut Rd, Durban Central</string>
    <string name="havana_grill">Havana Grill</string>
    <string name="address_havana_grill">42, Suncoast Casino, Battery Beach Rd, North Beach</string>
    <string name="unity">Unity</string>
    <string name="address_unity">Silvervause Centre, 117 Silverton Rd, Musgrave</string>
    <string name="mozambik">Mo-Zam-Bik</string>
    <string name="address_mozambik">198c Florida Rd, Windermere, Berea</string>

    <!--String used in the InfoFragment-->
    <string name="info_text">Durban (Zulu: eThekwini, from itheku meaning \"bay/lagoon\") is the largest
        city in the South African province of KwaZulu-Natal and the third most populous in South Africa
        after Johannesburg and Cape Town. Located on the east coast of South Africa, Durban is famous
        for being the busiest port in the country. It is also seen as one of the major centres of tourism
        because of the city\'s warm subtropical climate and extensive beaches. Durban forms part of the
        eThekwini Metropolitan Municipality, which includes neighboring towns and has a population of
        about 3.44 million. In May 2015, Durban was officially recognised as one of the New7Wonders Cities
        (together with Vigan, Doha, La Paz, Havana, Beirut, and Kuala Lumpur).
        \n\nRainbow nation is a term coined by Archbishop Desmond Tutu to describe post-apartheid South Africa,
        after South Africa\'s first fully democratic election in 1994. The term was intended to encapsulate
        the unity of multi-culturalism and the coming-together of people of many different nations,
        in a country once identified with the strict division of white and black.
        \n\nDurban is ethnically diverse, with a cultural richness of mixed beliefs and traditions.
        Zulus form the largest single ethnic group. It has a large number of people of British descent
        and has the most Indians of any city outside India. The influence of Indians in Durban has been
        significant, bringing with them a variety of cuisine, culture and religion. The faith-based
        conflict that is evident in many parts of the world is not reflected in Durban\'s religious landscape,
        where harmony is generally the order of the day.  While the legacy of apartheid is still with us
        in many ways, contemporary South Africa is a country of great tolerance and acceptance.</string>

    <!--Strings used in the AttractionsFragment-->
    <string name="moses_mabhida_stadium">Moses Mabhida Stadium</string>
    <string name="moses_mabhida_stadium_info">Activities include a Skycar ride or Adventure Walk to the
        top of the arch with 360 degree views over Durban; \nGuinness world record Bungee swing;
        \nSegway gliding tours of the stadium; \nCafes and Restaurants</string>
    <string name="kingsmead_cricket_ground">Kingsmead Cricket Ground</string>
    <string name="kingsmead_cricket_ground_info">is a major test match and one-day cricket venue</string>
    <string name="kings_park_stadium">Kings Park Stadium</string>
    <string name="kings_park_stadium_info">is host to the internationally renowned Sharks Rugby Team</string>
    <string name="ice_arena">Durban Ice Arena</string>
    <string name="ice_arena_info">Activities include leisure ice skating, birthday parties, school excursions,
        sporting events, teambuilding activities, corporate functions and group bookings</string>
    <string name="port_durban">Port of Durban/ Harbour</string>
    <string name="port_durban_info">Durban has a long tradition as a port city. The Port of Durban,
        formerly known as the Port of Natal, was an extremely busy port of call for ship repairs
        when the port was opened in the 1840s. Durban is now the busiest port in South Africa,
        as well as the fourth busiest container port in the Southern Hemisphere.</string>
    <string name="rickshaws">Rickshaws</string>
    <string name="rickshaws_info">Durban is known for its iconic Zulu rickshaw pullers navigating throughout
        the city. These colourful characters are famous for their giant, vibrant hats and costumes.
        Although they have been a mode of transportation since the early 1900s, they have been displaced
        by other forms of motorised transport, and the 25 or so remaining rickshaws mostly cater to tourists.</string>
    <string name="uShaka">uShaka Marine World</string>
    <string name="uShaka_info">with Wet \'n Wild water park and uShaka Sea World - the fifth largest aquarium in the world</string>
    <string name="bunny_chow">Bunny chow</string>
    <string name="bunny_chow_info">Durban is famous for it\'s Indian food, most notably the Indian food known as
        the "bunny chow". Ironically the bunny chow, doesn\'t have rabbit meat, it only has beef stuffed in bread.</string>

    <!--Strings used in the NatureFragment-->
    <string name="botanic_gardens">The Durban Botanic Gardens</string>
    <string name="botanic_gardens_info"> was established in 1849. The oldest such park in Africa, it
        includes a selection of well-established trees and a small indigenous forest. The gardens are
        home to the rare cycad Encephalantos woodii and includes a lovingly maintained orchid house,
        an informative visitors centre and a charming coffee shop. Located on Durban\'s Berea,
        with a pond and beautifully landscaped lawn at its centre, it's the perfect place for
        a stress-free family outing.</string>
    <string name="hawaan_forest">Hawaan Forest Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="hawaan_forest_info">is a 110 hectare stretch of forest middle of residential
        Umhlanga that has survived the process of urbanisation. The reserve is a beautiful example of
        coastal lowland forest that includes many rare trees as well as a number of small indigenous
        animals such as bushbuck, bushpig, duiker, mongoose and guinea fowl. Facilities include a picnic
        area, guided walks, binding and game viewing.</string>
    <string name="pigeon_valley">Pigeon Valley Nature reserve</string>
    <string name="pigeon_valley_info">is located near the city centre in the suburb of Bulwer and is
        readily accessible from Mazisi Kunene Road. This small park contains many large indigenous trees,
        including the Natal Elm, and preserves something of the original coastal forest environment.
        A good birding site for forest birds in particular, the park includes short trails on both sides
        of the valley, through which a small stream runs.</string>
    <string name="bird_park">Umgeni River Bird Park</string>
    <string name="bird_park_info"> is home to more than 400 different species of bird. With a strong
        emphasis on conservation and education, the park features birds from North and South America,
        Africa, Indonesia and Australia while the Cockatoo Café, situated in the heart of the bird park,
        provides visitors with delicious breakfasts and light lunches. In 2009 the eThekwini
        Municipality agreed to purchase the Umgeni River Bird Park from its previous owners Tsogo Sun
        Gaming, rather than allow it to close down.</string>
    <string name="krantzkloof">Krantzkloof Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="krantzkloof_info">offers breath-taking views of the spectacular
        gorge system created by the Molweni and Nqudu Rivers. There are a number of marked self-guided walks
        available through this amazing natural landscape. The reserve includes many rare plants as well as
        frequent close-up sightings of eagles and falcons. Braai facilities are available as well as
        guided walks and guided birding and game viewing.</string>
    <string name="burman_bush">Burman Bush</string>
    <string name="burman_bush_info"> is a nature reserve in Morningside. Among the forest trees that populate
        the reserve are flat-crowns, the forest fever-berry and red beech. It contains three walking trails,
        that wind through the forest and allow visitors to see the various flora and fauna. A viewing platform
        at the outer walk\'s northern extremity allows sweeping views of the Umgeni River, from Connaught bridge
        to the Blue lagoon. Reclusive species constitute much of the fauna. The reserve has Durban\'s largest population
        of blue duiker, besides grey duiker, banded and slender mongoose, porcupines and troops of vervet monkeys.</string>
    <string name="new_germany">New Germany Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="new_germany_info">is a protected area of coastal grassland and forest overlooking the suburb
        of New Germany outside of Pinetown, Durban. The reserve consists of a nature park featuring a walk-through
        aviary and snake display, and grasslands to the south of the park which can be explored by foot.
        The reserve is home to a number of bird species, including the Natal robin and purple-crested Turaco.
        Small mammals such as the blue and common duiker, impala, and mongoose are also found in the reserve.</string>
    <string name="umhlanga_reserve">Umhlanga Lagoon Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="umhlanga_reserve_info">is a 26 hectares nature reserve on the shore of the Indian Ocean
        at Umhlanga Rocks, South Africa. The reserve encloses the Ohlanga River\'s lagoon and mouth.
        The forest forms a natural extension of the less accessible Hawaan Forest, of which the greater
        part lies inland of the busy M4 road. The reserve trails start at a car park at the northern end
        of Lagoon Drive, Umhlanga. The reserve has picnic sites, the remains of a prehistoric shell midden
        and walking trails, with a walkway and pedestrian bridge that span the lagoon.</string>
    <string name="mitchel_jameson">Mitchell Park &amp; Jameson Park</string>
    <string name="mitchel_jameson_info">are located at the top of Florida Road. With its majestic trees
        and beautifully manicured flower beds, Mitchell Park is a popular spot for family outings.
        Across the road is Jameson Park, which is home to a mass of beautifully maintained rose bushes
        and which provides a wonderful view of the city.</string>
    <string name="palmiet">Palmiet Nature Reserve</string>
    <string name="palmiet_info">has a diversity of birds and plants living among its gentle waterways,
        grasslands and cliffs. With a small area of Saligna woodland, the reserve is a lovely spot to
        while away an afternoon and learn more about local fauna at the Interpretive Centre. The reserve
        is also an historic site and includes part of the original wagon route from Durban to Pietermaritzburg.</string>

</resources>
